Seino! The skinny channel! This time I'm too flippant!
This year, today, I'd like to do a surprise!
Oh, you mean you're going to put on a show?
That's right.
Earlier, when we were talking about various things...
I made you nervous.
You are the caller.
Today, I'm on the caller's side.
I wanted to make the announcement in front of the camera.
I didn't tell you until now.
I see.
Today.
What is it?
Who do you think you can tell?
Kira, right?
She's challenging herself to eat super spicy food.
I've been told you're filming a project... about Kira.
Right now.
But...
She said it's really sweet.
Very sweet.
I heard it's not spicy.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
She didn't like it.
I think we might have had a little talk.
That's why it's so sweet.
That's how it's supposed to be.
Uh...
I don't think so.
So even if you eat the Kira one...
It's really spicy.
Okay, okay.
But you know what?
Let me try something else.
If I let her eat this, she'll know.
No, you can't do that!
Now, I'm going to make both very sweet and very spicy.
Both? Both?
They say we have to be even hotter than this.
Why the hell are we in this?
I don't know, I just found out today.
What do you mean? I don't think I can eat this alone.
So, you know, you should just make it so spicy that I can't talk or something.
I know it's sweet, but I can't... wait a minute.
I can make it sound like I can't listen to it anymore.
Here it is.
Self-mutilation.
You know, I'm not even good at spicy food.
I went to Shin-Okubo for work the other day.
I put everything in!
I had a hot-pot dish, but it was pretty spicy even for a hot-pot dish.
Even the ones that didn't say "super spicy"...
I don't want to put all of it in!
Wow!
Well...
You know what's wrong with Yoko right now?
I'm super hungry.
That's why I want to eat so much!
I want to eat, but there's no way I can enjoy such spicy food.
Spicy food is spicy to begin with!
Well, let's add some more.
Here you go, raayu.
Seriously? What's Tabasco? It's spicy.
Tabasco is supposed to be sour and spicy.
Can I get away with a little bit of shichimi?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Stop it, really stop it.
Stop it.
You're so cute.
No Tabasco?
Yeah, I don't want to.
I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna do it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You'll know when you put it in. You'll understand when I get you in there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Idiot.
Idiots! We're on our own! Don't be stupid!
That kind of project, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ah!
What? Huh?
He's strong. He's strong.
This is not the plan, today.
Who's the first one?
Okay, I'm going to go ahead and make it a little spicier.
The aroma is too strong!
Give me a break!
I'll make it quick because it's going to stretch!
This is Yamaguchi Killer's ramen!
I thought it was good, but... you put a little bit of it in, so the colors match.
Color matching... but I'll say it from the beginning, so color matching!
That's right.
You definitely don't want to put too much of this.
It'll turn black.
I've never done this before. I've never done this before.
Oh, Bear!
That's enough, that's enough.
It blends in, it blends in, it blends in.
No, it's not going to blend.
Blend in.
I've never done this before. Just go for the off-color stuff.
Yeah, you're gonna have to be aggressive with this one.
That's good. That's good.
You can do better than that.
Killer. Sorry.
It's killer.
This is a project for killer.
Sounds fun.
But don't worry, it blends in with the red powder.
A little bit of this, a little bit of that, and we'll adjust.
Yeah.
It's fun just to make something for other people, right? I know you enjoy just making things for other people, so let's just...
Let's put it all in.
Let's change the colors. Let's change the colors.
I don't get it. I don't get it.
I know what you mean.
No, I don't want to make you suffer like that.
You'd be surprised how little you know.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I don't want to mix it up.
It's like really spicy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Apologies first, to Killer.
To Killer's family, relatives, and fans of Killer, including Killer
Please forgive me for making you eat something terrible.
I'm sorry.
We eat spicy food too, but...
Yes, please forgive us.
Seino! Let's GOGO!
Today, we're going to do a very hot and spicy food show!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's my first time.
First time! First time!
Yes, sir.
We've got someone who's done it before.
Just look at us modelling!
I don't know what level you're at.
I'm hungry... once... even...
I'll do my best!
Let's go for it!
Start!
Oh, my God.
The smell is bad.
The smell is already a little bad. It's so bad.
Let's put the membrane on, together.
Oh, once, once, once.
One time, one time, one time.
Once we put the membrane on Once the membrane is applied
Apply the membrane to the stomach
One at a time.
Then apply the membrane to the stomach.
Stomach membrane.
What? You feel like you're going to go?
It smells so bad.
Oh, my God.
Aaaaah!
Oh, no!
And it's kind of...
It's black and a little bit sooty.
I won't do it!
Shut up, baby!
I'll do it!
Just say a few more words and get him to do it.
Take another drink.
I love milk.
One time, one time, one time.
One time that's all it takes.
Why can't you just let it go?
Why can't you just let go of your tears?
What, why?
Oh, I'm coming, it's rotten.
Is it black?
Wait a minute, what?
Um, it's a totally different color.
They're the same.
I think they taste the same.
Just listen to the smell.
Try it.
Wait, it doesn't look anything like that.
Do you see it?
It's the same.
No juice in front of your eyes, right?
No juice. No, there's no juice. Juice. Oh, I don't have any juice.
Juice?
Maybe it's the juice.
Because I made too much for you.
Oh, I see.
I'll have some then.
Okay. Bon appétit.
Oh, my God, I'm going to eat it now!
It's too spicy!
I can't!
Ryoka, look, doesn't Kira's look spicy at all?
What? Why?
But look, we'll eat it together.
Try it once.
Oh, this...
It's not hot anymore.
Okay, let's go.
You want to go?
Yeah, let's go.
Ready?
Yeah. - Ha-ha-ha.
Ciblet's here. Oh, it's good. It's good.
Something sweet. Something sweet.
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here. It's not here already.
It's not mixed in, it came in a lot later, but I mixed it a little bit, and this is what I got.
It's sweet. It's mixed in. It's mixed in.
I'll give it one more try. I'll try to be more reactive.
I don't know if it's really spicy, but it's better than "beyoung"!
Oh, here it comes! It's spicy! It's really spicy! It hurts!
It's okay.
Why isn't it coming?
Wait, I didn't expect salt.
It's really hot.
It's not spicy at all?
It's not spicy at all. It's sparkling hot. I don't like spicy food.
I don't like hot sauce. Talk to me.
It's sweet.
Is it that one? A little bit. Isn't that it? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Is that it?
It's sweet, really.
Really. - What? It's not spicy?
It's very spicy.
What? Not too spicy? Not at all.
It's spicy.
It's hard.
No fever today?
Are you okay?
It's painful.
Why don't you try eating again?
Why don't you try it from here?
It's really spicy.
It's very spicy.
But it's deliciously spicy.
I'm hooked.
How is it? Not too spicy?
It's hot.
Oh, my God.
Birthday of the Strongest Girl!
Wait, wait, wait!
Let's go with Kira as the leader.
Please eat him once!
Please eat this one too.
Looks spicy.
What a stupid lie!
It was a sweet surprise.
We're the same age, so we used to stand up together.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but I'm sure it's sweet.
I'm sorry. I'm sure it's sweet.
I've never said that before.
It's not big, Meyer. It's spicy.
I've never done this before... but I'll show you in the video later.
I'm just gonna make a video of it later, okay?
I'm sure it's not big, but it's spicy! I'll put it in the fiscal year's list, and it's really delicious and sweet, in case you were wondering.
I've got a social networking video too, so watch that and calm your mind.
I wanted to eat curry... but you didn't react well.
I'm going to eat it again.
I'm not good at this.
It's not good, it's not good, it's not good!
I was trying to match her, but she was matching me.
I was matching him, but he was matching me.
I often stopped thinking about it once when I ate some Kiran.
I had to wait for him to make it right.
It's painful. It's painful.
It was good. I put a lot of chocolate in it.
So...
It's good, it's good, it's good.
How was Kira?
I'm glad I got a surprise.
I don't think it's a surprise. It's my first time.
I don't think it was a surprise.
I thought it might be rotten, but I didn't know what to do, so I just ate it.
Kira, all the reports about Kira are true.
Everything you're wearing is true. You're lying! I know it's true!
It's true! I'm glad!
So, that was a surprise. Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you very much.
If you liked this video and think Kira is a good girl, please give us a high rating, comment and subscribe to our channel!
Bye bye!
This time I'm wearing a costume made by dholic!